For our meerkats, we're going to have to take it in two different steps.
First off, we need to paint the rockery, and we're going to need to let that dry, and then we'll paint the meerkats on top of it.
So, let's get our paint ready, and we're going to start filling in this area.
So let's dip our brush in and get a nice big dollop of paint; making sure that the paint's not dripping too much from off off the brush, or at least you have a good drop cloth down.
If you're kind of sick and tired of some of the detail work we've been doing, the rocks are very excellent therapy, cause' we're just going to basically plaster this with a nice matte; very, very light brown, maybe a touch of purple and pink in here, with some pink-red highlights to basically, kind of go back over the edges.
I'm not even worried too much about the rocks shape at this point, because they'll be very easy to rediscover underneath the paint.
Of course, you can leave these a little bit thinner if you're worried about making sure the, where the lines are.
Otherwise, just go to town and slop it on.
Make a nice thick coat.
We're going to try to definitely avoid having to put on two coats here, because you don't have to do a lot of the detail work which can make the paint smear.
So again, just keep expanding up from the central area, and once you get towards the top of the rocks, like up in here, you may choose to like get a, you know, a smaller brush to get more of the detail on here.
Usually the rocks are a little bit bumpy and lumpy, so actually, unlike most of the rest of the painting, I find myself remaining comfortable with a bigger brush, even towards a lot of the edges.
Now you could actually get up here higher, where you start getting into the feet in the meerkat details.
I may go down a brush to make sure I don't accidentally paint over the feet, cause I only want to be, make sure I can still see those lines when I do move to paint the meerkats later on.
So you're going to continue this throughout, and you're going to let it dry, and then we're also going to add in some pink highlights, which I will demonstrate next.